agriya.com 2016-03-13

# Privacy Policy - Agriya

[](https://www.agriya.com/) Agriya establishes its highly remarkable **ABS software** \- **A clone of ZocDoc** [Click Here](http://customers.agriya.com/solutions/zocdoc-clone)

[Home](https://www.agriya.com/ "Home") » Privacy policy

## This is the Privacy Policy for Ahsan Technologies

### Our Contact Information is:

New no 61, Plot no 39, second street,   
Kamdar Nagar,  
Mahalingapuram,  
Nungambakkam,  
Chennai - 600 034.  
Tamil Nadu.  
India.  

We do not collect any information about our visitor's email or referring domain.

### For visitors on our website we collect:

  * The email address and personal information from visitors who post on our website.
  * The email address and personal information from the visitors who communicate with us via email.
  * The email address of those who post in our chat areas.
  * Aggregate (General Tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site.
  * Any information given to us by users that contact us via inquiry form, survey, etc.

### The information that we collect is used for:

  * Internal review, tracking, or contacting and is then archived for future reference.
  * Improving the quality of our website content and user friendliness for a better user experience.
  * Not Shared with any outside organization for commercial purposes. We may still share this information for tracking and other non-commercial purposes.

### We may use a standard technology called a cookie for the following purposes.

  * Recording Session information for shopping cart or other purposes.
  * Store visitor preferences for return visits to our website.
  * Helping manage subscriptions or private areas on our website.
  * Record user specific tracking or aggregate tracking information of visitors on our website.
  * Alert visitors to our live help console, or offering live help to website visitors.
  * If you are currently receiving a newsletter or emails from us and would like to stop receiving them, please notify us by contacting us by email, at the above address.
  * We do not partner or use any 3rd party ad services or content delivering services.
  * With respect to security, we use industry standard encryption technologies, when transferring and receiving data from visitors on our website.
  * With respect to sensitive information, we will redirect the user to a secure page either on our site, or to a trusted 3rd party site before transferring or receiving sensitive data. This information may include credit card or banking information, medical information, or other sensitive information.
  * For questions regarding our privacy policy or website in general, contact us through phone, email or snail mail, on the above listed addresses.
